Okayama...
I want to challenge you!
We have a birthday!
Wow!
Wow! We ran! We ran so fast!
You're so beautiful!
What?
I have a live concert in Okayama, and the nature near the live house is so beautiful,
I'd like to go for a walk there today!
It's so beautiful, but...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What's that? Did we really come here?
What? Oh! This place is amazing!
Oh! This place is so beautiful!
What? That area over there...
By the way, if you go to the right, there is a park,
There are geeks lined up in rows of six different categories,
I was so surprised when I saw a wild peroring,
You'll like me even more,
So today, we're going to go somewhere where the nerds won't find us...
Wow! The bridge is flowing like crazy! The river! The water!
We have to keep it out of...
This place is scary...
This area is so beautiful!
I went to that cherry blossom path!
The path of cherry blossoms is fantastic! A beautiful girl could stand there!
I'm a beautiful girl, so I look good, but my clothes are a little too casual today...
I really have to borrow some clothes from Ao-nyan!
Beautiful!
Can I take a picture then?
Then take the shot!
Then take a picture!
Please take a picture of MJ in full Japanese!
Yes, thank you!
Wait a minute! When I'm at Akihabara Life, you know, I'm going by this team,
My head is a little like this...
Sorry! Over here!
Oh! They're right behind us!
Then is that SK-CD?
Customer name!
So you're saying that some people like this because it's super commercialized?
I recommend it!
Here I am in this funny outfit!
Is this, is this a limited edition from Okayama?
Yes, only in Okayama!
If you don't come to Okayama, you'll never eat it again!
I'll take this one!
Yes! I think it's good!
By the way, why do I recommend it so highly?
Oh, but...
It's better than...
More than you thought?
Oh no! Oh, no!
That's delicious!
It's delicious! It's...
Better than I thought?
The salad on top of the bokkan sushi!
Oh!
It's delicious!
Delicious! Delicious!
For this?
Yes!
And as you roll it up...
Oh! That's really great!
Oh, you take it like this.
From the back...
Yes!
Okay, hold on.
It's going to be okay.
Sorry!
I think I might move to spray!
Move to spray!
Oh, no!
Oh, you want to use the star?
You want me to use the star?
Oh, it's in my eye! Ouch!
Oh, God, you do that with the case.
Oh, no!
No!
Okay, I'm off!
No, no, no!
No!
No, no, no, no!
Did anything interesting happen when you went to get the fish?
Oh, you were...
You were in...
I was just...
Sorry, I didn't hear you.
I can't stomach it.
I can't...
Are you kidding me?
It really hurts, doesn't it?
I don't know what's going on.
Can I just be a cunt?
What's wrong?
Oh, my God.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, God. Oh, God...
Oh, God, oh, God...
I'm waiting!
I see...
I thought the moe and the emoting was lost on you.
Lost...
The day after tomorrow is my birthday!
Wow!
The first song you all gave me!
I thought I was in a field of things when you all shook your heads!
Thank you so much!
Please take care of me today!
No, your voices are the best!
I'm really chewing on this tour, aren't I?
For the past three years...
I've been holding back from listening to your voices for the past 3 years.
I was happy to be able to play live, but
I was happy to be able to do the shows, but I also felt lonely.
And you don't even tell us.
And I was worried, but...
But I'm having so much fun at the show!
Yay!
Well, today is the last show of the tour.
Today is the 6th show of the tour!
Aaah~!
I can't believe I've been to this many shows!
Six shows?
That's right.
Oh! Niigata City Road, Nagoya!
Oh, no!
No, but, you know, when there's an end...
Doesn't that mean there's a beginning?
Time for the last spurt!
Yay!
This is now, now let's step out
The sky is flying and the wind is blowing big
I mean I've got a caber in the sky
Sometimes I fly Sometimes I fly
Shake on shake
Step out with me, spark life
Step on it, step on it, play on it, play on it
Shake on, shake on, shake on
Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Yeah! Yeah!
Come on, you're the heroCome on, you're the hero
Ginsenbar, come on. One wave, one step.
You're a big boy, just keep going and you're all right
Smile, it's a legendary adventure
Oh!
Here we go.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Have a good day.
I made a mistake.
Good night.
You're sweating.
See you.
Shuten, Shuten. Encore.
Bye bye!
Good morning everyone. It looks like you can still dance all over the country.
Find me the best cherry blossoms.
Let's go!
Yes, it's okay.
Here we go.
There you go.
I threw a piece of it.
I just want to cut it up a little bit.
How about this?
How's that?
End of the line.
The end.
Three days to go!
How'd it go?
Three times.
It's got a lot of charm.
Three more days!
It's started. It's started.
It's on! It's on!
But still... I changed a couple of things.
We're still evolving.
It's gonna evolve.
Oh, man.
We're changing. We're changing.
The change is not over. I'm not going to do it.
I'm not gonna do it.
Twenty-two. Two thousand two hundred and twenty-three.
Okay?
I wasn't flying anymore.
We're gonna practice. We're gonna sing a song.
Practice, practice, practice.
Thank you for watching.